Hello, everyone!
We're Super Excited 7-Eleven, and we're
here to rock your heart!
I'm Kanamin, aka Tsujino Kanami, from
Super Excited Blue.
I'm Anjou, aka Chari, from Super
Excited Purple.
I'm Hitaka, aka Hitomu Hitachi, from
Super Excited Red.
I'm Haruka, aka Haru, from Super
Excited Pink.
I'm Aki, aka Suda Aki, from Super
Excited Lemon.
I'm Hiyorin, aka Yoshikawa Hiyori, from
Super Excited Green.
Nice to meet you!
Today, we're going to do MBTI test,
which is popular in Korea.
MBTI test is a test that helps you to
know your personality type and your
future lifestyle.
The test is to see how you see the
world and how you adapt to it.
It's a test to make sure who you are.
Who are we?
We're going to see what we're like.
Let's get started!
Please subscribe to my channel!
We'll start first!
I'm excited!
Shall we?
We'll do the personality test!
Do you feel that you're not good at
introducing yourself to others?
What?
I often get absorbed in my own thoughts
and ignore or forget things around me.
I don't like to introduce myself to
others.
Thank you for watching my video.
Don't you have another chance?
Rather than that, I think that it's
more important to be wise to make and go
towards what you want to do
Than that I have to work efficiently
So what's planning wants us to do?
It's the same
What?
The middle?
You start something from a completely
curious mind.
Wait.
You start something from a completely
curious mind.
What's the difference?
Curiosity.
I thought you said you don't have
curiosity.
You start something from a completely
curious mind.
You sound like a person who uses a
pitch.
What do you mean?
You start something from a completely
curious mind.
No, I'm not.
When there are a lot of people, I avoid
the middle and stay close to the wall.
When you walk in nature, you often fall
into your own trap.
I'm like, I'm going into that world.
I have a lot of them.
I imagine a lot.
I'm like, I'm going into that world.
Q. What is the reason for your
existence?
What is the reason for your existence?
Isn't it hot?
I'm like, I'm going into that world.
I imagine a lot.
Can you imagine?
I can.
I imagine a lot.
I'm ESFJ.
I'm ESFJ, too.
I'm looking forward to it.
We've finished the live show.
Let's see the result.
See you next time!
Watch out!
Wow!
ESFJ-T
I'm ESFP-T
I'm ENFJ-A
Totally different!
I'm looking forward to it!
We'll read the details later!
Me too!
I'm ENFJ-B
Now, we have the results!
I'll open this one.
ESFJ-A
ESFJ-T
It's the same!
I'm ESFJ-T.
I'm T.
Kito-chan is the same.
It's so similar!
I'm ESFP-T.
I'm ENFJ-A.
It's totally different!
Only this part is the same!
So, we have the results here.
I can't read this alphabet, so I'll
read it.
Kanami, you can read it.
It's so similar!
It's amazing!
I'm ESFJ-T.
I'm ENFJ-T.
I'm ENFJ-A.
It's so similar!
I'm ENFJ-T.
I see.
It's so similar!
I'm ESFJ-T.
Thank you?
I'm so happy!
What's this?
I'm ESFJ-T.
It's so hot!
We're so similar!
We are, though.
I'm ESFJ-T.
Where are you from?
I'm from the sea.
I'm ESFJ-T.
You're so similar!
You're so good at this.
If you're unhappy with your friends,
family, or people around you, you're
unhappy, too.
Really?
It means you're kind.
You're sad, too.
You can't keep a cool atmosphere.
That's interesting.
I didn't know that.
It's a detailed answer.
I was surprised when I saw the answer.
It's like a mini-game.
Next.
Is it the same?
It's the same.
I see.
We're ESFJ-A and we're ESFJ-T.
Next.
You're kind and sympathetic.
You're sociable.
It's the same.
I think it's similar to Kanamin.
It's similar.
It's almost the same.
It's the same.
All three of us are the same.
What?
That's amazing.
All three of us are the same.
But we're not that similar.
There's a difference between T and A.
A is self-assertive.
T is tall.
A is Kanamin.
Self-assertive.
You're kind and sympathetic.
You're sociable.
There's a difference.
T and B are self-assertive.
You're easy to notice.
You're assertive.
You're sensitive.
You're easy to get depressed.
You're focused.
You're energetic.
You're nervous.
You're fun and affectionate.
I see.
T is tall.
Me and Kiyo-rin are A.
We're self-assertive.
T is tall.
Me, Aki-chan and I are tall.
I think I can tell.
I see.
It's interesting.
I think so.
You and Julia had almost the same
result.
Did you have any differences?
Julia,
I often asked the same question to the
11th member.
I did.
I regretted it after I said it.
I see.
Do you have any differences?
I don't know.
We're quite different.
We're active in a group and we're good
at what we do.
We're good at what we do.
I'm not sure.
But, we don't like to break our plan.
We want to do our job well.
It's amazing.
It's amazing that you and KON-chan have
the same result.
How many did you get?
16 patterns.
It's amazing.
I wonder what's the difference between
us.
We're the same.
We'll be the same in a year.
I'm quite different from the three of
you.
We have different sentences.
I'll go next.
I'm a person who is open-minded,
realistic, emotional, and free.
I see.
I'm a person who is energetic and
pleasant.
I'm good at trying new things.
I'm not hesitant.
I'm the most conspicuous person.
Actually.
I was hiding it, but I'm actually.
I'm not good at thinking about things
in detail.
I'm a person who is shy.
I'm not.
I'm a person who is easy-going.
I'm a person who likes people.
Sometimes, I'm too playful and it
becomes a problem.
I can't say anything.
I'm honest with my feelings and I'm a
person who cares about people I like.
I'm a person who is friendly.
What's wrong with you?
You're trying to sympathize with her,
aren't you?
I'm quite shy.
You're quite shy, aren't you?
I'm a person who wants to share what
I've experienced.
I'm a person who is open-minded.
I'm a person who is quick-witted.
I'm a person who is easily intimidated
by others.
I'm a person who is easy-going.
I'm glad you said that.
I do everything I want to do.
I do everything I don't want to do.
It's easy to understand.
It's funny.
I'm a person who is bored when I'm
alone.
I'm a person who has to do something
all the time.
I hate the silence when there are many
people.
I'm quite clear.
I'm a person who tries to see the pros
over the cons.
I'm a person who is friendly to people
I meet for the first time.
I agree.
I'm a person who is self-centered.
I think I was told that in my previous
diagnosis.
Let's move on to Aki-chan.
I'm a person who is a fan of I.F.L.J.
I'm a person who is a fan of O.N.N.J.
Thank you for watching.
I'm a fan of O.N.N.J.
You can't go to their concert.
You can only go to their concert when
they are in a concert hall.
I'm a fan of O.N.N.J.
Thank you for watching.
You have a personality.
I'm a fan of O.N.N.J.
Thank you for watching.
I'm not good at this.
Are you OK?
I agree.
If you buy a book, you can read it from
the beginning to the end without
skipping.
I agree.
I read manga and other characters.
I read books at home.
When you do something, you should clean
up the surroundings first.
I agree.
I clean up the surroundings when I
study.
I see.
I clean up the surroundings at home.
I agree.
I talk to my friends once a month.
I talk to my friends when I feel hurt.
I agree.
I'm kinder than strict.
I talk to my friends when I feel like
I'm being bullied.
I agree.
I like to read books.
I think you read a lot.
I read a lot.
I'm going to read a book.
I'm not good at reading.
I like older people.
I like my family.
I agree.
I don't get angry when I talk to my
family.
I want to hide my feelings.
What?
I see.
I'm not good at reading.
I like to listen to others.
I like to talk to others than to read.
I like to do my best rather than
reading.
Do your best.
I don't want to cause trouble.
I don't like to get close to others.
I'm not good at human relationships.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
I like to have a stable relationship
rather than a stimulating one.
I worry that I might do something wrong
if I don't have a good relationship.
I agree.
I worry about myself.
I often get angry at others.
I often remember what others said.
I agree.
Aki-chan is like this.
I'm not good at reading.
What?
She is kind.
I agree.
I can see that she is kind.
The last one is Iori-chan.
I'll do it.
Wait a minute.
What are you doing?
Iori-chan, what are you doing?
I'll do it.
I didn't know that I could get this.
This is A from ENFJ.
She is friendly and has a clear sense
of values.
She is considerate of the future and
the reality at the same time.
She is great.
She is sociable and has a good
personality.
She is popular with people around her.
She is a good person.
In Japan...
In Japan, she is easy to be used by
people.
She is just and has a good sense of
justice.
She is good at encouraging and
supporting people.
She is a good person.
She is honest and responsible.
She is good at taking care of people
around her.
I wonder if people around her can see
this.
I think people around her want to
support her.
I think so, too.
I'll do it.
She is persuasive and can make people
feel better through Japanese magic.
She is great.
She is a leader and is one step behind.
She is like a leader.
She is a leader.
She is easy to be used by people around
her.
She is a good person.
She has a good personality.
She is good at talking.
She likes to talk.
Do you like to talk?
I love to talk.
But, I don't know if I'm good at it.
You are interesting.
Thank you.
She is able to talk more than she
thinks.
Maybe I'm correct.
I think you are right.
She is able to talk more than she
thinks.
I think so, too.
She is good at taking care of others.
She is good at interfering others.
She is good at criticizing herself.
I want to say that.
I think that's the best.
I wrote it down in my diary.
I will give you a hint.
1. She is very noisy.
2. She wants to be a party person.
I think she is right.
3. She is good at guiding others.
4. She likes to be guided.
5. She is simple and strong-minded.
6. She likes to spend her hobby time
alone.
She likes to spend her hobby time
7. She is reliable.
8. She is easy to get along with
others.
9. She knows herself well.
10. She is interested in work and wants
to be a party person.
I want to do many things.
11. She is quick-witted.
12. She is quick-witted.
She is quick-witted.
13. She is easy to get hurt.
She is a party person.
It's interesting.
She is scary.
She is scarier than I thought.
She is a party person.
I thought she was a party person.
I saw her.
We write this in our CV.
We can write this on Instagram.
Yes, we can.
We can write it on Instagram.
It's interesting.
It's on the fan page of CHO-TOKUSEN.
I like her personality.
It's interesting.
I heard that she got a personality
test.
It's like a role-playing test.
It's like an entertainment test.
It's like a test for the main
character.
We did MBTI test today.
I got to know more about your
personality.
I found out that you are like this.
It was interesting.
It might be fun to do it alone.
We usually do it with our family.
It might be fun to do it with everyone.
Please try it.
If you think this video is good or
interesting, please subscribe to this
channel and click the good button.
Please leave a comment.
Thank you for watching.
Please subscribe to this channel.
Bye bye.
I'll go at full speed without braking.
So, please keep up with me.
I'm a laughing rice, dan-dan-dan
Kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss
kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss
kiss
You are the reason I exist
I can't stop this feeling, I can't stop
To the point where it's impossible, to
the point where it's impossible, I want
to love you strongly
Ready, set, go!
I want to be able to stay away from
you, a spell
To the point where it's impossible, to
the point where it's impossible, I want
to love you strongly
Ready, set, go!
I want to be able to stay away from
you, a spell
You're in love too, right?
Love Love Love!
Please subscribe to our channel!
Why is it that when it rains,
I always seem to be the one crying?
I wonder if I can't walk without
washing away my dirty thoughts?
Come on, let's go anywhere
Goodbye, goodbye, me of yesterday
The city lights in the rain sparkle
My heart is like a sunny day,
I play the piano in the rain
I wonder why, when I smile, the world
seems to shine
I can turn my umbrella and be relaxed,
because I can't walk without it
Surely, someone is crying from
somewhere, and I'm getting wet from
somewhere again
I wonder if it's cold
Surely, someone is crying from
somewhere, and I want to share my
feelings
The scenery I don't know is still in
front of me, so let's go anywhere
Goodbye, goodbye, thank you for
yesterday
The city after the rain is colored
I'll draw a fragment of the future on
the canvas of my damaged heart
It will guide me
Now I can say it, the reason for my
tears
When I'm lost, I remember it right away
Even if it rains, I'll smile
Look, let's go anywhere
Goodbye, goodbye, to me of yesterday
The city after the rain is sparkling
My heart is like a sunny day, the sound
of the rain drops
I play the rainbow piano
Goodbye, goodbye, to me of yesterday
The city after the rain is sparkling
My heart is like a sunny day, the sound
of the rain drops
I wear a rainbow dress
Please subscribe to my channel!